TAYLOR BLAKE

2222 Rucker Ave, Apt. J. Everett, WA 98201 · (949)500-9355 misstaylorann08@yahoo.com · LinkedIn ·

I am an experienced Account Manager/Executive with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing, advertising, and sales industries. I have a can-do attitude and I excel at thinking outside of the box when it comes to problem solving. I'm a self-starter and I do best in an environment where I don't need much supervision and can work independently. I'm a firm believer in teamwork and helping my colleague's complete tasks. I love to learn new things and pick up new things quickly. I thrive in a constantly changing environment and I'm great at anticipating needs.

EXPERIENCE

5/3/2019 - 3/20/2020

SENIOR ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE, DEALER EPROCESS WEST

Dedicated Senior Account Executive who excels at client communication, support, and willingness to do what it takes. I assisted a multitude of VIP clients with daily tasks to assure their websites were performing well and leads were being generated at a high level with a fantastic conversion rate. Daily tasks included, but were not limited to: assisting with the design and launch of new accounts and websites, sales and implementation of new products, training dealers how to use website and inventory dashboards, assisting with the set up of Craigslist and Facebook Marketplace, monthly performance reviews and audits, generating reports to assist dealers in learning what's working for them and how we can bring them to the next level, working with dealers on pricing and inventory, and any other request my VIP clients needed help with.

1/15/2019 - 4/8/2019

ACCOUNT MANAGER AND FACILITIES COORDINATOR, COAST WORKPLACE SOLUTIONS

Responsible for overseeing and completion of planned maintenance and on demand projects for several commercial companies nationwide. My responsibilities included, but were not limited to project management, procurement of new vendors, coordinating project proposals between my customers and vendors, asset management, and account management.

5/7/2018 - 1/15/2019

ASSISTANT LEAD SALES COORDINATOR, IT LUGGAGE

Responsible for overseeing and completing different divisions of work done within the North American sales office, including but not limited to: sales reports, order confirmation documents, packaging sheets, POS completion, travel plans and itineraries, office wide expenses and accounting, buy documents, and general clerical work. I also assisted various corporate clients (i.e. retail department stores, large e-commerce companies, off-market stores) with any needs they may have while going through the initial and repeat order process.

7/16/2017 - 4/27/2018

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT, BURNHAM GIBSON WEALTH ADVISORS

Responsible for the pre-filling, processing, and case management of any new life insurance client; handling and processing of sensitive documents, including but not limited to: loans, distributions, death claims. I was promoted to this position after 5 months of working for the company.

8/16/2015 - 7/16/2017

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT, AXA ADVISORS FOR SINA SOLTANI

Responsible for the processing and case management of sensitive documents (i.e. life, annuity, loan, hardship, distribution applications); daily client contact and appointment settings; light general office work.

EDUCATION

JANUARY 2018

BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION, ORANGE COAST COLLEGE

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, Powerpoint)
- CRM applications Salesforce and Redtail
- Client relationships and customer service
- Insurance and Wealth Management
- Medical Terminology
- Social Media + Marketing